by RentAnAdviser.com
Murda on the beat so It is not nice
For this life I cannot change
Hidden Hills‚ deep off in the main
M&M′s‚ sweet like candy cane
Drop the top‚ pop it let it
bang (Pop it‚ pop it)
For this life I cannot change
Hidden Hills‚ deep off in the main
M&M′s sweet like candy cane
Drop the top‚ pop it let it
bang (Pop it‚ pop it)
Drop the top play hide and seek
Jump inside‚ jump straight to the leak
Take a sip‚ feel just how I breathe
On freeway‚ but no ain′t nothin′
free (straight up)
Bend laws‚ bend lanes
Been bustin′ bills‚ but still
ain′t nothin′ change
You in the mob soon as
you rock the chain
She caught the waves just thumbin′
through my braids (alright)
Heatin′ up‚ baby‚ I am just
heatin′ up (It is lit)
Fiji lover‚ now they indeed
that is impressive
Fill his cup now you know
how they keep me up
Icy love‚ icy like a hockey puck
For this life I cannot change
Hidden Hills‚ deep off in the main
M&M′s sweet like candy cane
Drop the top‚ pop it let it
bang (Pop it‚ pop it)
For this life I cannot change
Hidden Hills‚ deep off in the main
M&M′s sweet like candy cane
Drop the top‚ pop it let it
bang (Pop it‚ pop it)
All the ones‚ all the chains
piled on the mantle
All the dogs‚ all the dogs low creep
right behind me in the Phantom
Never go‚ never go dip on
this estates santana
Yeah‚ run it back turn the lights
on when I hit up Green Lantern
Yeah‚ fly the broads‚ fly the
dogs down to Atlanta
Yeah‚ in the cut in Medusa
lay low I might be
Yeah‚ roll up help me calm down
when I move in high speed
Yeah‚ If I send one need the text back
′cause you know what I need
Oh please (oh please)
Oh me (oh me)
Oh my (oh my)
We been movin′‚ we been movin′
for some time (Alright)
Flexin′‚ flexin′ try to exercise
Exercise‚ exercise‚ exercise‚ exercise
For this life I cannot change
Hidden Hills‚ deep off in the main
M&M′s sweet like candy cane
Drop the top‚ pop it let it
bang (Pop it‚ pop it)
For this life I cannot change
Hidden Hills‚ deep off in the main
M&M′s sweet like candy cane
Drop the top‚ pop it let it bang
by RentAnAdviser.com